A Guide to the Karen Darner Legislative Papers, 1990-2004
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
L. Karen Darner Legislative Papers, 1990-2004
The Library of Virginia
51365
15.525 cubic feet (35 boxes)
Darner, L. Karen, 1945-
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
THIS COLLECTION IS LOCATED AT THE STATE RECORDS CENTER. CONTACT ARCHIVES RESEARCH SERVICES FOR ACCESS INFORMATION, DIRECTIONS, AND HOURS.
Acquisition Information
Gift of L. Karen Darner, Arlington, Virginia, 24 July 2014.
Biographical Information
To be added.
Scope and Content
To be added.
Contents List
- Series I. Legislative session files, 1990-2004., Extent: 29 boxes. (Box 1-29)
  Chronological.
  - 1991 session and election season.
    - Campaign, 1990-1991 (Jan. 1991 special election). (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Campaign, Nov. 1991 election. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Campaign questionnaires, Nov. 1991 election. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - HB 1989 - Waiting period for handgun purchase. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - HB 2006 - Absentee ballots. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - HB 2007 - Dillon Rule. (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
    - HB 2009 - Parking ticket debt. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - HR 58 - Teacher contracts. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Handgun research. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Press. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Report from Richmond newsletter, Feb. 1991. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 1991 Session of the Virginia General Assembly, Summary and Review. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1992 session.
    - Abortion. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Abortion (Stambaugh files). (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HB 45 - Human rights. (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
    - HB 272 - Professional corporations. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - HB 379 - Scope of practice, audiology and speech pathology. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - HB 422 - Recycled paper. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - HB 725 - Hiring practices (Gentleman's Agreement #2). (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - HB 726 - Abindgon Plantation House ruins/Washington National Airport. (Box 3, Folder 1-8)
    - HB 726 - Abingdon Plantation House ruins/ Washington National Airport. (Box 3, Folder 9-10)
      Includes material related to HJR 475 (1991 session).
    - HB 727 - Licensure. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - HB 738 - Election laws. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - HB 751 - Labor Day. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - HB 884 - Dental hygienists. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - HB 885 - Local taxes and license fees (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - HB 2008 - Parking tickets. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - HJR 97 - Joint subcommittee to study the needs of foreign-born residents of the Commonwealth. (Box 4, Folder 7-10)
    - HJR 159 - Smoke-free workplace. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - HJR 160 - Subcommittee on hiring. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Press. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1993 session and election season.
    - Campaign. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Candidate questionnaires. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Crime/gun control package. (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
    - Dillon Rule and local government. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - HB 1436 - Windshields. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 1522 - Ramps on curbs. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - HB 1940 - Dry cell battery recycling. (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
    - HB 2199 - Collaborative decision-making for school divisions. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - HB 2391 - Tuberculosis. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - HB 2392 - Collective bargaining, state employees. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - HB 2393 - Environmental tobacco smoke in the workplace. (Box 6, Folder 3-6)
    - HB 2398 - Carjacking. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - HJR 425 - Age-appropriate information for children re: phases of criminal justice system. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - HJR 426 - Custody of children with incarcerated parents. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - HJR 488 - Voter study. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - HJR 595 - Gender equity. (Box 6, Folder 11-12)
    - HJR 660 - Needs of foreign-born individuals in the Commonwealth. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - HJR 661 - Foreign language interpreters in civil cases. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - HJR 662 - Licensure reciprocity. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - HJR 663 - AIDS insurance. (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - HJR 702 - Bottle recycling study. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Procurement. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Proposal to build Redskins stadium in Arlington. (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
    - Smoking in public schools. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Virginia General Assembly 1993 Session Summary. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1994 session.
    - Children of incarcerated parents. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Disney's America proposal. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - HB 175 - Court service records. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - HB 249 - Smoke-free schools. (Box 8, Folder 2-5)
    - HB 408 - Social security numbers on driver's license. (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
    - HB 454 - Board for Hearing Aid Specialists. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - HB 485 - HIV/AIDS insurance. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - HB 960 - Spousal rape. (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
    - HB 962 - Animal clinics and care. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - HB 2247 - Notification of pesticides. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HJR 24 - Pesticide study. (Box 9, Folder 3-5)
    - HJR 66 - Comprehensive study of confidentiality. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - HJR 87 - Equal Rights Amendment. (Box 9, Folder 7-9)
    - HJR 114 - Deaf and hard of hearing. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - HJR 114 - Deaf and hard of hearing. (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
    - HJR 262 - Needs of foreign-born individuals in the Commonwealth. (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
    - HJR 263 - Interagency immigrant and refugee policy council. (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
    - HJR 276 - Public access to legislative information. (Box 10, Folder 7-8)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Northern Virginia Mental Health Institute. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Press. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Trailer reflectors. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Virginia General Assembly 1994 Session Summary. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Washington National Airport/Abingdon Plantation site. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Women's issues/Equal Rights Amendment. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1995 session and election season.
    - Budget amendments. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Campaign. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Candidate questionnaires. (Box 11, Folder 5-7)
    - HB 728 - Free textbooks. (Box 11, Folder 8-11)
    - HB 1695 - "Crimes Against Nature" law reform. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - HB 1845 - HIV insurance / HB 2013 - AIDS insurance. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - HB 1988 - Prevention/early intervention. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - HB 2100 - Braille instruction. (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
    - HB 2101 - Collective bargaining, state employees. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - HB 2151 - Arrest and return of a parolee to detention. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - HB 2231 - Parking tickets. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - HB 2248 - Virginia Indoor Clean Air Act amendment, nursing homes. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - HJR 541 - Medical savings accounts. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - HJR 599 - Needs of foreign-born persons in the Commonwealth. (Box 12, Folder 11-12)
  - 1996 session.
    - Cooperative extension. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (1996-1999). (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - HB 65 - Truancy provision of welfare reform. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - HB 243 - Retail sales/use tax, exemptions for organizations providing services to mentally handicapped. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - HB 380 - Parking tickets. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - HB 381 - Bus idling. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - HB 382 - Utility marking. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - HB 472 - Disabled veteran license plates. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - HB 482 - Conditions of employment. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - HB 689 - Pedestrian safety. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - HB 690 - Transportation for students with disabilities. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - HB 811 - Virginia Indoor Clean Air Act/local ordinances re: smoking. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - HB 1021 - Location of routes by the Commonwealth Transportation Board. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - HB 1127 - Pregnancy and employment discimination. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - HB 1148 - AIDS insurance. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - HB 1149 - Local grievance procedure. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - HB 1150 - Local cigarette tax. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - HB 1151 - Trigger locks on guns. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - HB 1152 - Sale of handgun ammunition to minors. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - HB 1466 - Substance abuse treatment provider licensure. (Box 14, Folder 6-8)
    - HJR 230 - Employee assistance. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - HJR 315 - Commending the Arlington County Civic Association. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Immigrant and Refugee Policy Council. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Report from Richmond. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - TACTS (The Arlington Community Temporary Shelter). (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - 1997 session and election season.
    - Abortion, (1997-1998). (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Campaign. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Candidate questionnaires. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - HB 487 - Department of Housing and Community Development training re: the homeless. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - HB 554 - Indoor plumbing assistance program. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - HB 1591 - Sales tax on food. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - HB 1592 - Disabled veteran license plates. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - HB 1633 - Liquidated damages for violation of vehicle weight limits. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - HB 1725 - Retail sales/use tax, exempt medical/educational organizations. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - HB 1844 - Retail sales/use tax, exempt organizations providing emergency medical assistance. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - HB 1861 - Retail sales/use tax, exempt organizations providing services to the mentally disabled. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - HB 1862 - Pedestrians and vehicular traffic. (Box 15, Folder 12-14)
    - HB 2179 - Virginia Interagency Action Council on the Homeless. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - HB 2180 - Industrial development authorities. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - HB 2264 - Employee Assistance Program professional licensure. (Box 16, Folder 2-4)
    - HB 2291 - Cigarette tax. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - HB 2434 - Clean indoor air, public schools. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - HB 2463 - Parking fines, rented vehicles. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - HB 2530 - Enforcement of tobacco laws by ABC special agents. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - HB 2631 - Sale of handgun ammunition to minors. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - HB 2718 (etc.) - Sodomy reform. (Box 16, Folder 10-12)
    - HB 2719 - Police privacy. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - HB 2721 - Licensure of substance abuse treatment professionals (1-2 of 3). (Box 16, Folder 14-15)
    - HB 2721 - Licensure of substance abuse treatment professionals (3 of 3). (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - HB 2746 - Issuance of permits for reservoirs. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - HB 2901 - Political subdivisions meeting/conferring with employee associations. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - HJR 582 - Equal Rights Amendment. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Pesticide safety, public buildings. (Box 17, Folder 5-7)
  - 1998 session.
    - Arna Valley (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - HB 170 - Local cigarette tax; statewide for localities. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - HB 171 - Sales and use tax; repeal of tax on certain food. (Box 17, Folder 10-12)
    - HB 172 - Sales and use tax; increase on watercraft and airplanes. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - HB 235 - Amendment to Standards of Quality. (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
    - HB 447 - Defacement of structures. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - HB 448 - Credit for excessive water or sewage charges. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - HB 453 - American Radio Relay League license plates. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - HB 584 - Governmental employee associations. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - HB 916 - Infant hearing screening. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - HB 919 - Income tax credit for caregivers. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - HB 920 - Child safety locks on guns. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - HB 1071 - Law enforcement employees' records. (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - HB 1115 - Information technology access for blind and visually impaired. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - HB 1211 - Location or alteration of routes by the Commonwealth Transportation Board (1-2 of 3). (Box 18, Folder 13-14)
    - HB 1211 - Location or alteration of routes by the Commonwealth Transportation Board (3 of 3). (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - HJR 163 - Consumer credit info to college students. (Box 19, Folder 2-4)
    - HJR 164 - Secondhand smoke in public schools. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - HJR 171 - Quick court. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - HJR 203 - Equal Rights Amendment. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - HJR 204 - Regulation of electrologists. (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
    - Transportation. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Virginia General Assembly 1998 Session Summary. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - 1999 session and election season.
    - Campaign. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Disabled parking. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Efforts to remove SSN's from driver's licenses. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - HB 1478 - Tax credit for caregivers. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - HB 1505 - Marital property. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - HB 1610 - Local government revenue. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - HB 1837 - Student representatives to local school boards. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - HB 1974 - Health care professionals, free clinics. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - HB 1975 - Licensed teachers for certain courses. (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
    - HB 1976 - Licensure of substance abuse counselors. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - HB 2071 - Jury costs in civil trials. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - HB 2264 - Handguns, informed consent and 24-hour waiting period. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - HB 2265 - State employee associations. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - HB 2631 - Condition on use of tobacco settlement funds. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - HB 2632 - Elder rights. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - HB 2633 - School board salaries. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - HB 2634 (old HB 1211) - Location or alteration of routes by the Commonwealth Transportation Board. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - HJR 567 - Potomac Yard transportation study. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - HJR 568 - Reagan National Airport. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - HJR 669 - Study, merging Board of Audiology and Speech with Hearing Aid Specialists. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Request for amendment to HB 1450 re: Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - VRS bill. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - 2000 session.
    - American Association of University Women. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations - budget info. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Budget amendment - Clasika Theatre. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Budget amendment - daycare. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Budget amendment (HB 1260) - funds for community counseling and treatment to juveniles in detention centers. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Budget amendment - Signature Theater. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Hatch Act info. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - HB 232 - Tax exemptions - Central American Resource Center. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - HB 233 - Tax ememption - National Alliance for the Mentally Ill. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - HB 380 - Preschool for at-risk children. (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - HB 422 - SSN's on driver's licenses. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - HB 556 - Adoption assistance. (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - HB 631 - Assessments of pupil performance in public schools. (Box 22, Folder 13-14)
    - HB 632 - Multiple criteria for assessement of pupil performance. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - HB 633 - Standards of Learning. (Box 23, Folder 2-5)
    - HB 634 - Governmental employee associations. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - HB 718 - "Crimes Against Nature" law, penalty. (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
    - HB 978 - Death penalty. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - HB 980 - Foster care tuition waiver. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - HB 1043 - Remediation. (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - HB 1260 - Children with mental illness. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - HB 1261 - Health coverage for biologically-based mental illness. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - HJR 30 - Local revenue sources. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - HJR 104 - Foster care study. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - HJR 181 - Equal Rights Amendment. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - HJR 182 - Impact of Virginia Public Procurement Act on local governing bodies. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - HJR 267 - Impact of public policies on minority families. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - HJR 268 - Corporate citizenship. (Box 24, Folder 8-9)
    - HJR 390 - Bruce Miller. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - 2001 session and election season.
    - Budget amendment, Arlington House. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Budget amendment, Barcroft Community House. (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Budget amendment, citizenship grant. (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Budget amendment, deaf outreach services. (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Budget amendment, HIV meds in local/regional jails. (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Budget amendment, U.S. women in the military. (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Budget amendment, West Nile virus. (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Campaign. (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Campaign financial reports. (Box 24, Folder 20-21)
    - Candidate questionnaires. (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Constituent correspondence, miscellaneous. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - HB 1 - Amendment proposal. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - HB 1621 - Million Mom March license plates. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - HB 1629 - Using cell phones while driving. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - HB 2103 - School crossing guards. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - HB 2122 - Graduation requirements. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - HB 2123 - Licensure of teachers. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - HB 2367 - Kinship care. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - HB 2554 - Provisional driver's licenses. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - HB 2653 - Child not responsible due to mental illness or mental retardation. (Box 25, Folder 10-11)
    - HB 2770 - Offender risk assessment instrument. (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - HJR 615 - Seating representatives of Virginia's Indian tribes as non-voting members of the General Assembly. (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Review of HB 1261 (2000). (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Standards of Learning. (Box 26, Folder 2-3)
  - 2002 session.
    - Budget amendments. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Child support info. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Children of incarcerated parents. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Dead Wrong: An Evaluation of Capital Prosecutions and Recommendations for Change, George Mason University, 2002. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - HB 47 - Graduation requirements. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - HB 130 - Urban highway construction allocations; traffic calming. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - HB 131 - Local government taxing authority. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - HB 132 - Gun-free school zones. (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - HB 133 - "Crimes Against Nature" law. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - HB 145 - Governmental employee associations. (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - HB 198 - Virginia Condominium Act; officers (same as HB 198). (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - HB 331 - Secretary of the Commonwealth; appointments. (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - HB 332 - Family Access to Medical Insurance Security Plan (FAMIS). (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - HB 638 - Driver's licenses and permits, identification cards. (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - HB 1044 - Unauthorized discharges; notification requirements (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - HB 1047 - Funding for elementary and secondary educational programs. (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - HB 1048 - Retirement benefits for teachers. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - HB 1049 - At-risk 4-year-olds. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - HB 1050 - Health insurance benefits, retired local school division employees. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - HB 1051 - License plates celebrating Virginia's Indian tribes. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - HB 1071 - Virginia Condominium Act and Virginia Property Owners Association Act; employee records. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - HB 1188 - Ridesharing. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - HB 1222 - Information on certain statewide referenda and bond proposals. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - HB 1246 - Placement of juveniles in secure local juvenile detention facility. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - HJR 11 - Equal Rights Amendment. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - HJR 165 - Virginia Commission on Youth study. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - HJR 166 - Medicaid early screening services info. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - House Committee on Education. (Box 27, Folder 12-13)
    - House Committee on Health, Welfare and Institutions. (Box 27, Folder 14-15)
    - A Legislator's Guide to Public Education in Virginia, Virginia Division of Legislative Services, December 2001. (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Public Education in the Commonwealth, Board of Education, January 2002. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Salute to Virginia state flag. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Southern Regional Education Board Legislative Work Conference, 22-24 June 2002. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Virginia General Assembly 2002 Session Summary. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - 2003 session and election season.
    - Budget amendment, child day care funding. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Campaign. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Council on the Status of Women (through 2005). (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Education-related tax credits. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - General Assembly Overview of Youth-Related Issues, Virginia Commission on Youth, 2003. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - HB 1482 - School accreditation. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - HB 1608 - Campaign finance disclosure. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - HB 1611 - Standards of Learning, non-public school students. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - HB 1612 - Juvenile not guilty by reason of insanity. (Box 28, Folder 13-15)
      Includes material re: former HB 25 (2002).
    - HB 1654 - Tax exemption, Fellowship Health Resources. (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - HB 1655 - Tax exemption, Fairfax Central Baptist Sunday School Union. (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - HB 1710 - Admissions tax. (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - HB 1711 - Watercraft/aircraft sales and use tax. (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - HB 1712 - Food and cigarette taxes. (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - HB 2570 - Governor's emergency powers; closed captioning of emergency news. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - HB 2571 - Governor's Board of Economists. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - HB 2573 - Firefighter benefits. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - HB 2628 - Pedestrian safety. (Box 29, Folder 4-5)
    - HB 2633 - School/student data. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - HB 2657 - Moratorium on executions. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - HB 2659 - Filing of birth certificates. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - HB 2733 - Support for committed juveniles. (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - HJR 564 - Youth Commission study, foster care payment rates. (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - HJR 565 - Accommodations for handicapped college students. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - HJR 566 - Youth Commission study, school safety. (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - HJR 567 - American Forests commendation. (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - HJR 587 - In-state tuition for immigrants. (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Session updates, newsletter. (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Standards of Learning. (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Special Subcommittees of the House Committee on Education, Undocumented Alien Students in the Commonwealth. (Box 29, Folder 17-18)
    - Virginia General Assembly 2003 Session Summary. (Box 29, Folder 19)